{
    "id": "0a36b59ce5fa45068d814dc504e9f8be",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There was ......................... anything to eat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hardly",
                "almost",
                "hard"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There ...................... a few boys playing in the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... at the door he demanded admission.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Knocking",
                "Knocked",
                "Having knocked"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind ................... a bit?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "moving",
                "to move",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Why donâ€™t you .................. listen to me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You need not ...................... on Sundays.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "to work",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ........................ his permission before using his computer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to seek",
                "seek",
                "sought"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Beethoven is greater ....................... composers of music.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than any",
                "than",
                "than most other"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer watching TV .................. reading books.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He used ................... poems when he was a student.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "write",
                "to write",
                "to writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}